{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of Netflix.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Who is Eleven?",
      "answers": ["Hero", "Villain", "Friend"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Netflix?",
      "answers": ["Stream", "Cable", "DVD"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Joe Exotic?",
      "answers": ["Zookeeper", "Singer", "Chef"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Bird Box?",
      "answers": ["Movie", "Series", "Game"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is BoJack?",
      "answers": ["Horse", "Dog", "Cat"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Bridgerton?",
      "answers": ["Series", "Movie", "Game"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Sabrina?",
      "answers": ["Witch", "Fairy", "Elf"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Narcos?",
      "answers": ["Series", "Movie", "Game"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Lucifer?",
      "answers": ["Devil", "Angel", "Demon"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Witcher?",
      "answers": ["Series", "Movie", "Game"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Geralt?",
      "answers": ["Witcher", "Knight", "King"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Ozark?",
      "answers": ["Series", "Movie", "Game"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Piper?",
      "answers": ["Prisoner", "Guard", "Warden"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Crown?",
      "answers": ["Series", "Movie", "Game"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Claire?",
      "answers": ["Queen", "Witch", "Singer"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Roma?",
      "answers": ["Movie", "Series", "Game"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Klaus?",
      "answers": ["Santa", "Elf", "Witch"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is You?",
      "answers": ["Series", "Movie", "Game"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Joe?",
      "answers": ["Stalker", "Detective", "Doctor"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Witcher based on?",
      "answers": ["Book", "Game", "Movie"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
